<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<course1>
    <programming>
        5 major types of programming languages Procedural
                    programming languages. A procedural language follows a
                    sequence of statements or commands in order to achieve a
                    desired output. ... Functional programming languages. ...
                    Object-oriented programming languages. ... Scripting
                    languages. ... Logic programming languages.
    </programming>
    <cricket>
        What is cricket management course? An academic course that
                    embraces the cricket season and has been developed in
                    consultation with a range of cricket industry experts. Two
                    placement opportunities in year 3 and 4 of the course
                    (domestic and/or international) 4 years focused on cricket
                    coaching, management development leading to a Masters
                    qualification.
    </cricket>
    <karate>
        Martial arts are codified systems and traditions of combat
        practiced for a number of reasons such as self-defense;
        military and law enforcement applications; competition;
        physical, mental, and spiritual development; entertainment;
        and the preservation of a nation's intangible cultural
        heritage. The practice of basic techniques Right after the
        warm-up ends many karate classes begin with basic practice.
        This includes drilling stances, punches, kicks, blocks and
        strikes on the spot and up and down the floor with the focus
        being on multiple repetitions of the main techniques
        required for each rank level.
    </karate>
    <danace>
        What is a dance course? It is both a physical and academic
                    study of performance, choreography and artistry. By earning
                    this degree, students are guided towards a greater knowledge
                    of dance through focus on the physical, technical,
                    communicative and artistic aspects of the craft.
                    What is the importance of studying dance? Studying dance
                    develops creativity, teamwork, confidence, critical
                    thinking, self-discipline, physical health and the ability
                    to work collaboratively—all beneficial in any 21st century
                    career path and quality of life
    </danace>
    <vollyball>
        Course Description: This course is designed to develop/teach
                    basic skills and knowledge in the game of Volleyball.
                    Students will learn fundament skills and rules in order to
                    enhance their knowledge, performance, and understanding for
                    the game of Volleyball.
    </vollyball>
    <invesmnet>
        In finance, the purpose of investing is to generate a return
                    from the invested asset. The return may consist of a gain
                    (profit) or a loss realized from the sale of a property or
                    an investment, unrealized capital appreciation (or
                    depreciation), or investment income such as dividends,
                    interest, or rental income, or a combination of capital gain
                    and income. The return may also include currency gains or
                    losses due to changes in the foreign currency exchange
                    rates.
    </invesmnet>
</course1>