<?xml version="1.0"?>
<school>
        <campus>
                Our school is one of the biggest and most famous schools in the
                country and of course its represent a model for an ideal school. Our
                school stands on the Buriganga. The campus covers about 50 Acores to
                land. The school is housed in six four-storied buildings. There is
                the main gate at the entrance where the gatekeepers control the
                unauthorized entrance of people and vehicles. The headmaster’s room
                is in the central building. The southern building is used for
                official works. The eastern building is used as the laboratory and
                the library. Student’s common room stands on the north side of the
                campus. Other buildings around the campus are used as classrooms.
                There is a large taken at the entrance of our school campus. A large
                grassy lawn and a garden in front of the principal’s room add to the
                beauty of the campus. We like our school campus very much.The
                southern building is used for official works. 
        </campus>
        <library>
            is a place where one can find a huge collection of books,
            periodicals, etc. My school library is huge. It has two big rooms.
                    One room has books arranged neatly on shelves. Another room is
                    called the reading room. It has tables and chairs where students sit
                    and read books. Mrs. Reet Rathod is our librarian. She is very
                    strict about maintaining discipline in the library. We need to
                    maintain silence in the school library. In my school library, we
                    have various types of books- fictional, non-fictional, literature,
                    books on general knowledge, etc. I love to read storybooks and books
                    on general knowledge which have colourful illustrations. Books in my
                    school library are arranged in such a way that students can find
                    them easily.We are allowed to borrow at most three books from the
                    school library at a time. We need to return the books within three
                    weeks from the date of issue. I feel blessed to have a library in my
                    school.I feel blessed to have a library in my
                    school.
        </library>
        <event>
            A school organises many events where students can participate. These
                    events help the students to discover their talents. It is always a
                    happy and memorable moment to participate in these events. My
                    favourite event is the Annual Function. It is organised in the month
                    of September in my school. This year I participated in Drama. The
                    event name was “The Mirage”. It told the story of a Fisherman and
                    his greedy wife. I played the role of a Golden Mermaid. On that day,
                    our teachers asked us to do makeup at home and then come to
                    school.All the drama students were then given the costumes. We all
                    then went to the backstage. The event began after the parents took
                    their seats. First, the prizes were distributed to the students. I
                    got a certificate for holding second position in Essay writing
                    competition. Then our Principal announced on the stage that the
                    story – ‘The Mirage’ will begin. The story began and after that a
                    dance performance took place.
        </event>
        <sport>
                Our school conducts sports day every year. It takes place in the month of November every year. Each year, all the classes present different acts to the audience. As per the class, the acts are chosen.

For instance, the junior classes perform simple acts like aerobics while the senior classes perform difficult acts like forming pyramids, long jump, and more. The sports day at my school takes place with full preparation.

The preparations begin two months earlier so that students can perfect their act. We get extra time to practice for the sports day. It also helps to cut down on some academic studying which everyone enjoys.
All of us practice in the sun and try to perfect our moves. On the final day, we all invite our parents to watch us perform our act. The parents come excitedly and watch and film their children perform harmoniously with the other students.
        </sport>
</school>